// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the output for 'python ' [-3]&",
    answer: "'h'",
    options: [
      "'o'",
      "'t'",
      "'h'",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which method is used to display a warning message in Python?",
    answer: "Tkinter.messagebox.showwarning('message here')",
    options: [
      "Tkinter.message.showmessage('message here')",
      "Tkinter.message.sshowwarning('message here')",
      "Tkinter.messagebox.showwarning('message here')",
      "None of the above"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is the special symbol used in python to add comments?",
    answer: "#",
    options: [
      "$",
      "//",
      "#",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which function overloads the >> operator?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    optioens: [
      "more()",
      "gt()",
      "ge()",
      "None of the above"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which operator is overloaded by the or() function?",
    answer: "|",
    options: [
      "||",
      "//",
      "|",
      "/"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of these is not a core data type?",
    answer: "Class",
    options: [
      "Lists",
      "Dictionary",
      "Class",
      "Tuples"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Given a function that does not return any value, what value is shown when executed at the shell?",
    answer: "None",
    options: [
      "int",
      "bool",
      "void",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following function convert a string to a float in python?",
    answer: "float(x)",
    options: [
      "int(x [,base])",
      "long(x [,base] )",
      "float(x)",
      "str(x)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which function displays a message on the screen in Python?",
    answer: "print()",
    options: [
      "sys.out.println()",
      "print()",
      "writeln()",
      "console.writeln()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How do we remove an element from a list?",
    answer: "list.remove()",
    options: [
      "list.delete()",
      "list.delete(-1)",
      "list.remove()",
      "list.remove(-1)"
    ]
  },

];